{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947422238307","data":{"timestamp":" 947422238307"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000109_155024"," gameId":" null"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" null"," tutorId":" null"," matrixName":" null"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" null"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" null"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947422245192","data":{"timestamp":" 947422245191"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000109_155024"," gameId":" null"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" null"," tutorId":" null"," matrixName":" null"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" null"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" null"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947422253654","data":{"timestamp":" 947422253654"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000109_155024"," gameId":" null"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" null"," tutorId":" null"," matrixName":" null"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" null"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" null"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:400..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF100-BL1.decr.104__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947422292899","data":{"timestamp":" 947422292899"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000109_155024"," gameId":" 8d210b65-a12a-4f8d-8111-c2be69b301e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_400..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF100-BL1.decr.104__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_650_650-691-700"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 650"," userResponse":" 650"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:400..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF100-BL1.decr.104__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947422309775","data":{"timestamp":" 947422309775"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000109_155024"," gameId":" 8d210b65-a12a-4f8d-8111-c2be69b301e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_400..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF100-BL1.decr.104__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_506_682-585-506"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 506"," userResponse":" 682"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:400..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF100-BL1.decr.104__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947422320821","data":{"timestamp":" 947422320821"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000109_155024"," gameId":" 8d210b65-a12a-4f8d-8111-c2be69b301e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_400..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF100-BL1.decr.104__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_506_682-585-506"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 506"," userResponse":" 585"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:400..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF100-BL1.decr.104__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947422329764","data":{"timestamp":" 947422329764"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000109_155024"," gameId":" 8d210b65-a12a-4f8d-8111-c2be69b301e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_400..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF100-BL1.decr.104__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_506_682-585-506"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 506"," userResponse":" 506"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:400..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF100-BL1.decr.104__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947422344702","data":{"timestamp":" 947422344702"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000109_155024"," gameId":" 8d210b65-a12a-4f8d-8111-c2be69b301e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_400..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF100-BL1.decr.104__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_770_770-482-725"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 770"," userResponse":" 770"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:400..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF100-BL1.decr.104__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947422401124","data":{"timestamp":" 947422401124"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000109_155024"," gameId":" 8d210b65-a12a-4f8d-8111-c2be69b301e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_400..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF100-BL1.decr.104__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_543_667-485-543"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 543"," userResponse":" 543"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:400..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF100-BL1.decr.104__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947422419293","data":{"timestamp":" 947422419293"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000109_155024"," gameId":" 8d210b65-a12a-4f8d-8111-c2be69b301e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_400..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF100-BL1.decr.104__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_696_696-857-615"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 696"," userResponse":" 696"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:400..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF100-BL1.decr.104__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947422435112","data":{"timestamp":" 947422435112"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000109_155024"," gameId":" 8d210b65-a12a-4f8d-8111-c2be69b301e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_400..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF100-BL1.decr.104__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_747_561-747-812"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 747"," userResponse":" 747"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:400..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF100-BL1.decr.104__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947422449239","data":{"timestamp":" 947422449238"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000109_155024"," gameId":" 8d210b65-a12a-4f8d-8111-c2be69b301e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_400..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF100-BL1.decr.104__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_552_552-642-783"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 552"," userResponse":" 552"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:400..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF100-BL1.decr.104__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947422463120","data":{"timestamp":" 947422463120"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000109_155024"," gameId":" 8d210b65-a12a-4f8d-8111-c2be69b301e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_400..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF100-BL1.decr.104__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_880_880-899-646"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 880"," userResponse":" 880"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:400..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF100-BL1.decr.104__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947422479232","data":{"timestamp":" 947422479232"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000109_155024"," gameId":" 8d210b65-a12a-4f8d-8111-c2be69b301e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_400..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF100-BL1.decr.104__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_666_666-755-882"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 666"," userResponse":" 666"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:400..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF100-BL1.decr.104__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947422492168","data":{"timestamp":" 947422492168"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000109_155024"," gameId":" 8d210b65-a12a-4f8d-8111-c2be69b301e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_400..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF100-BL1.decr.104__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_821_684-764-821"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 821"," userResponse":" 821"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:400..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF100-BL1.decr.104__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947422501973","data":{"timestamp":" 947422501972"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000109_155024"," gameId":" 8d210b65-a12a-4f8d-8111-c2be69b301e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_400..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF100-BL1.decr.104__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_821_684-764-821"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947422509721","data":{"timestamp":" 947422509721"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000109_155024"," gameId":" 8d210b65-a12a-4f8d-8111-c2be69b301e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_400..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF100-BL1.decr.104__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_821_684-764-821"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947422514595","data":{"timestamp":" 947422514594"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000109_155024"," gameId":" 8d210b65-a12a-4f8d-8111-c2be69b301e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_400..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF100-BL1.decr.104__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_821_684-764-821"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947422523889","data":{"timestamp":" 947422523889"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000109_155024"," gameId":" 8d210b65-a12a-4f8d-8111-c2be69b301e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_400..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF100-BL1.decr.104__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_821_684-764-821"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:400..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF100-BL1.decr.104__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947422540970","data":{"timestamp":" 947422540970"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000109_155024"," gameId":" 11adf69f-a573-4114-b2d6-bfaa7ed03619"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_400..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF100-BL1.decr.104__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_650_650-691-700"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 650"," userResponse":" 650"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:400..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF100-BL1.decr.104__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947422660381","data":{"timestamp":" 947422660381"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000109_155024"," gameId":" 11adf69f-a573-4114-b2d6-bfaa7ed03619"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_400..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF100-BL1.decr.104__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_696_696-857-615"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 696"," userResponse":" 696"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:400..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF100-BL1.decr.104__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947422691080","data":{"timestamp":" 947422691079"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000109_155024"," gameId":" 11adf69f-a573-4114-b2d6-bfaa7ed03619"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_400..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF100-BL1.decr.104__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_696_696-857-615"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"end":"end"}]}